【The fate that cannot be liberated】
【无法解脱的命运】
[Episode 20]
[第20集]
Madam has spent
夫人已经花了
After spending a few days in the pharmacy,
在药房待了几天，
And our young master just wants to
而我们少爷只想
See if she's okay.
看看她是否还好。
He won't cause any trouble.
他不会造成任何麻烦。
Can't you let him in?
你不能让他进来吗？
Come on, let's compete, let's fight.
来吧，我们来比赛吧，我们来战斗吧。
Chengbi, come in for a moment.
橙碧，进来一下吧。
I want to take a nap.
我想小睡一下。
Please help me check the error box.
帮我检查一下错误框。
We should distribute some herbs in the next few days
我们应该 在接下来的几天内分发一些草药
We need to pay close attention.
我们需要密切关注。
Ling.
凌.
We haven't seen each other for several months.
我们已经好几个月没见面了。
I wonder how you are doing in Jialin?
不知道你在嘉林过得还好吗？
I've finished all my work in Xunnan.
我在寻南的事都办完了，
The only thing I'm worried about is you.
我唯一担心的是你。
Like I said before,
就像我之前说过的，
If you are tired, exhausted,
如果你累了、疲倦了，
I can help you.
我可以帮你。
Let me help you write it.
让我帮你写吧。
Just like when we were in Wuhua Mountain.
就像我们在五华山的时候一样。
Thank you, brother.
谢谢师兄。
Best, Senior Brother Ren Yinxiao.
最好，任银霄师兄。
hurry up. Reaching for it again.
快点。再次伸手去拿它。
you...
你...
How do you...
你怎么...
Are you crazy?
你疯了？
wait.
等待。
Stop there.
停在那儿。
According to the young master’s pulse,
根据少爷的脉搏，
I can't say there's a huge improvement.
我不能说有很大的进步。
He still can't read or write
他仍然无法阅读或写作
And he can't understand complex words
而且他听不懂复杂的单词
This means his mental condition remains impaired.
这意味着他的精神状况 仍然受到损害。
Playing guzheng should be regarded as muscle memory.
弹古筝应该 算是肌肉记忆，
Just like many musicians can play with their eyes closed,
就像很多音乐家 闭着眼睛也能演奏一样，
And the tune is smooth.
并且曲调流畅。
the reason is simple.
原因很简单。
they are so familiar
他们是如此熟悉
The body has memorized the movements.
身体已经记住了动作。
So it's not surprising that the young master can play the piano.
所以少爷会弹琴也就不足为奇了。
but no matter,
但无论如何，
Being able to play the guzheng is a good thing.
能弹古筝是一件好事。
indeed.
的确。
My lord, the princess is here.
王爷，公主来访了。
The gift sent by the princess a few days ago
前几天公主送来的礼物
They are all too precious,
都太珍贵了，
I heard that it is only available in Astrology Pavilion.
听说只有 占星阁才有。
I'm about to send someone to return it.
我正准备派人去退货。
Unexpectedly, the princess came in person.
没想到公主竟然亲自来了。
After I gave the gift,
当我送出礼物后，
It is impossible to take it back.
想要收回是不可能的。
Moreover, it is specially prepared for the Xingxiang Pavilion.
而且，还是专门 为星象阁准备的。
If His Highness wants to do divination
如果殿下想占卜的话
Just send a notification.
只需发送通知即可。
Honorable Lord.
荣主。
Didn't anyone tell you?
没有人告诉你吗
I am visiting the capital this time
我这次访问首都
Is it actually about choosing a husband?
其实就是选老公？
Sir, the piano you ordered for the young master has arrived.
先生，您为少爷订的琴已经到了。
Rong Yu likes guzheng.
容玉喜欢古筝。
Did we bring anything to the capital this time?
这次我们有带东西到首都吗？
Yes we did. It's the dragon's roar.
是的我们做了。是龙吟。
Later it will be sent to the Astrology Pavilion.
稍后送到占星阁。
Yes.
是的。
Honorable Lord.
荣主。
i think i have
我想我有
I made it very clear myself.
我自己说得很清楚了。
At.
于。
uncle.
叔叔。
Let me introduce it to you.
我来给你介绍一下。
This is...
这是...
I know her.
我认识她。
do you know her?
你认识她吗？
I've met her before.
我以前见过她。
Master, do you know who I am?
少爷，你知道我是谁吗？
But we didn't exchange names last time, right?
但上次我们没有交换名字吧？
Maybe you're curious about me too?
或许你也对我感到好奇？
I saw her on the way to the capital.
我在去首都的路上看到了她。
She said she was looking for her husband.
她说她正在寻找她的丈夫。
You remember things like this very clearly.
这样的事情你记得很清楚。
She's staying for dinner tonight and you...
她今晚会留下来吃晚饭，你...
Uncle, I have to practice calligraphy tonight .
叔叔，我今晚要练书法 。
I will not bother you.
我不会打扰你。
I will skip dinner.
我会不吃晚饭。
Flatten, let's go.
展平，我们走吧。
Teacher Rong, I...
荣老师，我...
Be with Amakusa.
与天草同在。
Rong Yu will definitely get better.
容宇一定会好起来的。
please.
请。
This way.
这边走。
here.
这里。
Let him try it.
让他试试吧。
Just like last time.
就像上次一样。
Pick it up in a few days.
过几天再拿吧。
Master, can you still...
少爷，你还能……
Ate it?
吃了它？
water.
水。
Master, should I...
少爷，我是不是应该……
Zhangping, water.
Zhanping, water.
This is a role I recently learned.
这是我最近学到的角色。
You're always at the pharmacy.
你总是在药房。
You never come out, even to eat or sleep.
你永远不会出来，甚至吃饭或睡觉。
So I don't have time to show you.
所以我没有时间给你看。
unnecessary.
不需要。
If the instructor is right
如果导师说的对的话
Then that's it.
那么就对了。
There are still things in the pharmacy that have not been sorted out.
药房里还有东西 没整理好。
I have to go now.
我现在得走了。
If you feel unwell these days,
如果你这几天感觉不舒服，
You can ask Zhanping to come to me.
你可以让展平来找我。
Can't I go?
我不能去吗？
What?
什么？
Can't I come to you?
我不能来找你吗？
Why did you suddenly change?
你怎么突然变了？
Rong Yu.
Rong Yu.
If one day,
如果有一天，
I mean, if,
我的意思是，如果，
I did something to hurt you
我做了伤害你的事
would you do this again
你还会这样做吗
Hold on to me?
坚持住我吗？
Master, the princess is here.
少爷，公主来了。
I won't see her.
我不会见她。
So this is where Master Rong lives?
原来这里就是容少爷住的地方啊？
It does look unique.
它看起来确实很独特。
Who is this?
这是谁？
This must be He Jiuling.
这肯定就是贺九菱了。
Wait for you.
等你。
Our princess is looking for you.
我们的公主正在找你。
Sorry, but I have things to do.
抱歉，但我还有事要做。
Are you a maid from the Rong family?
你是荣家的丫鬟吧？
It seems like you have a pretty good attitude.
看来你的态度还不错。
I've been standing here for a long time
我已经在这里站了好久了
I'm tired
我累了
Your Highness, this is our lady.
殿下，这是我们的夫人。
Miss?
女士？
she looks tired
她看起来很疲惫
And it doesn’t look very dressed up.
而且看起来不太打扮。
I thought she was the cleaning maid.
我以为她是负责打扫卫生的女佣。
sorry. My fault.
对不起。我的错。
It doesn't matter.
没关系。
Your Highness, the young master needs to rest.
殿下，少爷 要休息了。
So he hasn't rested yet.
所以他还没有休息。
Our young master has rested.
我们的少爷已经休息了。
What about all these things?
所有这些事情又如何呢？
Just leave the food and drink to Master Rong directly.
吃的喝的， 直接交给荣爷就行了。
As for taking a boat,
至于坐船的话，
Our young master is ill and should not travel.
我们少爷病了，不宜出行。
Your Highness, you don’t have to come to visit me anymore.
殿下，您不必再来看望了。
Please leave the way you came.
请离开你来时的路。
let's go.
我们走吧。
Your Highness, our young master is resting.
殿下，我们的少爷正在休息。
Your Highness.
殿下。
I received an order from the king
我接到国王的命令
Don't allow anyone to bully you.
不允许任何人欺负你。
I can teach her a lesson.
我可以给她一个教训。
She just said a few words.
她只是说了几句话。
Why fuss over these little things?
何必为这些小事大惊小怪呢？
Rong Yu had too little.
容羽拥有的，实在是太少了。
If one day
如果有一天
I must leave him
我必须离开他
There can be another person by his side who cares about him and loves him,
可以有另一个人在他身边 关心他、爱他，
I will be forever grateful.
我将永远感激不已。
now i'm thinking
现在我在想
On how to take the next step.
关于如何采取下一步行动。
Can't wait for this
这可等不及了
Don't block my way.
别挡我的路。
You all move up
你们都动起来吧
I want to see your king.
我想见你们的国王。
Who is causing the riot?
是谁在制造骚乱？
Me, the son of Jialin's Lord Zhongyong.
Me, the son of Jialin's Lord Zhongyong.
It turns out to be the young master.
原来是少主啊。
Didn’t we already send someone to take you out?
我们不是已经派人送 你出去了吗？
How could I leave after everything that happened?
发生了这一切，我怎么能离开呢？
My sister traveled thousands of miles to find Nan to form an alliance.
姐姐不远千里来到 寻南结盟，
Not treated as a prisoner.
不被当作囚犯。
This is outrageous.
这太离谱了。
Breaking into the palace was a crime punishable by death.
闯入皇宫是一种 可判处死刑的罪行。
You, you Xunnan people, humiliate us.
你们，你们寻南人，羞辱我们。
Aren't you afraid that Jialin will raise troops to deal with you?
你就不怕家霖 起兵对付你吗？
There is nothing to be afraid of.
没什么好害怕的。
Xunnan has never been afraid of anyone.
寻南从来没有怕过任何人。
It's all the fault of Xi and the princess for provoking someone they shouldn't.
都怪羲和公主招惹了 不该招惹的人。
Also, young master, you don’t have to come again.
还有，少主，你不用 再来了。
Our king is not in the palace,
我们的国王不在皇宫，
He won't see you either.
他也不会见你。
Please leave.
请离开。
Recently, I often think about things from the past.
最近一段时间，我时常 想起过去的事情。
Master Wuhuashan,
五华山师父，
And you.
你呢。
Although you are all still here
尽管你们都还在这里
I'm scared
我很害怕
One day, even you will disappear.
有一天，连你也会消失。
Senior brother, I miss you.
师兄，我想你了。
is this real?
这是真的吗？
The Ministry of Rites is sending Rong Yu
礼部正遣容羽
Play music with me at the Queen Mother's birthday party?
在太后寿宴上和我一起演奏音乐？
Yes, every afternoon now, Master
是的，现在每天下午，少爷
I will take time to practice with His Highness.
会抽出时间跟殿下练习的。
Fortunately, before coming here,
幸运的是，在来这里之前，
My mother forced me to learn pipa for half a year.
妈妈逼我 学了半年琵琶。
That's the plan.
这就是计划。
Bring me my lute.
把我的琵琶拿来。
Your Highness,
殿下，
No lute.
没有琵琶。
You brought the Dragon Song Guzheng.
你带来了龙吟古筝。
Why isn't my personal Pipa here?
我的私人琵琶怎么没有在这里？
His Highness said
殿下说
Our palace cannot have you and Pipa at the same time.
我们王府不能 同时拥有你和琵琶。
Therefore, the Lord gave them all.
所以，主把他们都赐给了。
Then buy one.
然后买一个。
return,
还，
I am now
我现在是
A music lover.
一位音乐爱好者。
- do you understand? - Yes.
- 明白了吗？ - 是的。
Go quickly.
快去。
What's the matter with Lord Zhongyong?
忠雍大人有什么事吗？
No, the whole capital has been quiet recently.
这不，最近整个京城都很平静。
Teacher Rong,
荣老师，
From now on, every afternoon,
从现在开始，每天下午，
I will practice guzheng with you here.
我会在这里和你一起练习古筝。
If you don't say it, I'll take it as your consent.
如果你不说， 我就视为你同意了。
What should we do at the Queen Mother’s birthday party?
太后寿宴我们应该做什么呢？
I play the pipa very well.
我琵琶弹得很好。
Anything will be done.
任何事情都会做。
Master, don't be silent.
少爷，别沉默。
If you don't want to hear what the princess said
如果你不想听 公主说什么
Just nod.
只是点头。
What are your thoughts on this collaboration?
您对此次合作有什么想法吗？
If you find it difficult to choose,
如果你觉得难以选择，
I've chosen it for you.
我已经为你选择了。
This banquet is for everyone to enjoy music,
这场宴会是为了让大家 享受音乐，
So there is no need to choose difficult music,
所以没必要选择难的曲子，
correct?
正确的？
You are so easy-going
你真是太随和了
How about "Little Lotus"?
《小荷花》怎么样？
This piece is festive yet simple;
这件作品既喜庆又简单，
I'm very familiar with this.
我对此非常熟悉。
Do you want to hear it?
你想听听吗？
some parts are not perfect
有些部分并不完美
But the main thing is that this pipa is new.
但最主要的是这琵琶是新的。
I'm not used to it.
我玩不习惯。
What do you think of my playing?
你觉得我的演奏怎么样？
It’s okay, just say it.
没关系，就说吧。
Birds of a feather flock together.
物以类聚，人以群分。
I can accept all this.
我可以接受这一切。
what do you mean
你是什​​么意思
Did I play well?
是我玩得很好吧？
Your Highness.
殿下。
Your Highness, why are you running away?
殿下，你为何要逃走？
I need some fresh air.
我需要一些新鲜空气。
Do we want to go back to the young master?
我们要回少爷身边吗？
No, we don't.
没有，我们没有。
Now that I'm out, if I go back I will make people laugh.
现在我出来了， 再回去就会让人笑话。
We go home.
我们回家吧。
give it to me.
把它给我。
I'm going to go back and practice all night.
我要回去练习一整晚。
Miss, I need you.
小姐，我需要你。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
let's go.
我们走吧。
Miss He, please come in.
何小姐请进。
Senior brother.
师兄。
Your Majesty.
陛下。
I plan to see you tomorrow. Why are you here so early?
我计划明天见你。 你怎么这么早就来了？
Chengbi told me that you were stopped outside the city.
橙碧告诉我，你 被拦在城外了，
Almost got caught and taken to the Ministry of Justice.
差点被抓到并被带到 司法部。
Your hand is hurt.
你的手受伤了。
How can I feel at ease?
我怎能安心？
If I can't even handle these little things
如果我连这些小事都处理不了的话
What kind of Xunnan King will I become?
我会成为怎样的寻南王？
And it's not serious either.
而且也不严重。
I just haven't ridden a horse in a while
我只是好久没骑马了
My hands become fragile.
我的手变得脆弱。
There's no need to rush.
没必要着急。
I wrote you a letter a few days ago and you have arrived.
几天前我给你写了一封信 ，你已经到了。
Well, someone did say she missed me.
好吧，确实有人说她想念我。
How could an emperor be so willful?
一个皇帝怎么可以这么任性呢？
If you were taken as a spy and thrown into jail
如果你被当作间谍 关进监狱
I want to see what you will do.
我想看看你会做什么。
I'll just wait for my junior sister to save me!
我就等着我师妹来救我吧！
I'm not in the mood for jokes.
我没心情开玩笑。
You don't have to tell me.
你不必告诉我。
You're not doing well here.
你在这里过得不太好。
But you couldn't help but tell me.
但你却忍不住告诉我。
So something big must have happened
所以一定发生了大事
That's why I rushed over in such a hurry.
所以我才这么着急地冲过去。
Ling, what happened?
凌，到底发生了什么事？
It turns out
事实证明
That family Lin Xingxiang Pavilion
那个家林星象阁
Not just for show.
不只是为了表演。
They do have power.
他们确实有权力。
that's why
这就是为什么
I have to destroy the star map first.
我得先毁掉星图。
In this way, Rong Jiang will not be a threat by himself.
这样一来，容姜一个人就不会有什么威胁了。
my plan is
我的计划是
Create a new antidote and give it to Rong Yu,
制作出新的解药 交给容羽，
Before I went to visit an astrology center.
在我去参观占星馆之前。
This isn't like you.
这不像你。
What do you mean?
你是什​​么意思？
hesitated.
犹豫着。
Is it because of Rong Yu?
是因为容宇吗？
Ling.
凌.
Sometimes, the heart cannot be too soft.
有时候，心不能太软。
Rong Yu is from the Rong family.
容羽是容氏家族的人。
No.
不。
Rong Yu is Rong Yu, and the Rong family is the Rong family.
容羽就是容羽，容家 就是容家。
They are different.
他们是不同的。
how?
如何？
If he catches you using drugs to hurt him
如果他发现你 用药来伤害他
Will he still rely on you as he does now? Is he treating you well?
他还会 像现在一样依赖你，对你好吗？
His resentment towards you
他对你的怨恨
Bigger than Rongjiang River.
比榕江还大。
From the moment something goes wrong with the medicine,
从药出问题的那一刻起，
You two are destined to be enemies in this life.
注定你们两个 会是此生的敌人。
Of course it's about the medicine
当然是药的问题
It's largely my fault.
很大程度上是我的错。
I don't force you.
我不强迫你。
If you really can't do it,
如果你实在做不到，
let me.
让我。
I will avenge myself.
我会为自己报仇。
i want to cure him
我想治愈他
At least while his family is still here
至少当他的家人还在这里的时候
Even that family
即使那个家庭
Nothing more than a mirage.
无非是海市蜃楼。
This is the only thing I can do for him now.
这是我现在唯一能为他做的事了。
Of course, you can seek revenge.
当然，你可以寻求报复。
You also mentioned that Xingxiang Pavilion is really predictable.
你也提到星象阁 真的可以预测。
Various forces in the capital
京城各势力
The hunt is on for those responsible for the killing of rebel officials and traitors.
正在追捕那些杀害 叛乱官员和叛徒的责任人。
Have you ever thought that one day,
你有没有想过有一天，
Jiang Rong knows how to use star charts
姜蓉会用星图
And understand everything you do?
并了解你所做的一切？
for me,
为我，
Your safety is paramount.
您的安全是最重要的。
I have long since overcome my fear of death.
我早已克服了对死亡的恐惧。
What about those who are still alive?
那些还活着的人呢？
Those who are still alive?
那些还活着的人？
Our master and me.
我们的师父和我。
Don't you think we would be sad?
你不觉得我们会难过吗？
You have never visited an astrology parlor.
你从未参观过占星馆。
If you go there now and investigate the star map
如果你现在去那里 调查星图的话
Your unusual behavior
你这种不寻常的行为
It will inevitably arouse suspicion.
难免会引起怀疑。
When the star map is destroyed,
当星图被破坏时，
You're not the first suspect in Jiang Rong's eyes, are you?
你不会是 姜蓉眼中的第一嫌疑人吧？
Besides, you poisoned Rong Yu.
再说了，你还毒害了容羽。
So much is happening in the capital,
首都发生了这么多事情，
Even if he can't confirm it
就算他无法证实
He certainly won't let you live.
他肯定不会让你活着。
But I have the easiest access to star charts.
但我是最容易接触星图的。
Surveys do not necessarily require easy access.
调查并不一定 需要轻松访问。
I can send someone to help you.
我可以派人来帮助你。
Once we find out what a star map is
一旦我们找出星图是什么
and how to destroy it,
以及如何摧毁它，
I'll leave it to you.
我会把事情交给你。
This way, you can avoid any suspicion.
这样，您就可以避免任何怀疑。
OK
好的。
Thank you for your help, brother.
谢谢师兄的帮助。
There is no need for this between us.
我们之间没必要这样。
What's wrong?
怎么了？
Night falls.
夜幕降临了。
It's not even 5pm yet.
现在还不到下午 5 点。
And you've been here less than an hour.
而你到这里还不到一个小时。
Indeed, I have much to tell you.
确实，我有很多话要告诉你。
But Rong Yu just took the antidote I prepared.
但容羽只是服用了我配制的解药。
I worry that he might need me and not be able to find me.
我担心他可能需要我却找不到我。
So I'm a little anxious.
所以我有点着急。
I'm always in a hurry.
总是匆忙的我。
Now,
现在，
now you.
轮到你了。
Sorry, brother.
对不起，师兄。
I have arranged everything for Xunnan.
我已经把寻南的一切都安排好了。
This time, I want to stay in Jialin for a few more days.
这次，我想在嘉林 多呆几天。
Be careful on the road.
路上要小心。
Bye now.
再见了。
Master, don't think too much.
少爷，你别想太多。
Madam has just become distant from you.
夫人只是对你变得疏远了
Because she has been in a bad mood recently.
因为她最近心情不太好。
women are not always
女人不总是
Menstruation occurs once in a month,
一个月内有一次月经，
When they like to make a lot of trouble about nothing?
当他们喜欢无事生非的时候？
Zhanping.
Zhanping.
Do you remember the royal wedding reception five years ago?
你还记得五年前的皇家婚宴吗？
I do.
我愿意。
On the way back to the villa,
当时回别墅的路上，
You were intercepted by Madam on the way.
你半路被夫人拦截了。
At that royal banquet,
在那场皇家宴会上，
original engagement
原来的订婚
It's for him and her.
是为了他和她。
It was me who intercepted Jiuling halfway.
半路拦截九灵的是我。
She hadn't smiled like this in a long time.
她已经很久没有这样笑过了。
but I...
但是我...
I always seem to make her cry.
我好像总是让她哭。
Where were you just now?
你刚才去哪儿了？
We were just...hanging out at the mansion.
我们只是……在宅邸里闲逛。
The young master is not in a good mood.
少爷心情不太好。
not feeling good?
感觉不好？
No, not really. Nothing serious...
不，不是真的。没什么严重的事...
The room was a bit stuffy.
房间有点闷。
When I returned to the room later,
稍后回到房间时，
Open a few more windows.
再打开几个窗口。
I'm going to the kitchen to make some mung bean soup.
我要去厨房 煮点绿豆汤。
Why are you doing all these things?
你为什么要做所有这些事情？
Why did you give them grapes and money?
你为什么给他们葡萄和钱？
You want to limit me before we get married.
你想 在我们结婚之前限制我。
Rong Yu, I don’t want to marry you.
容钰，我不想嫁给你。
I thought you were an elegant gentleman
我以为你是一位优雅的绅士
But you are a big liar and a scoundrel.
但你就是个大骗子和无赖。
Who likes a liar?
谁会喜欢骗子呢？
Have you never liked Rong Shao?
你从来没有喜欢过容少吗？
There is no never.
没有永不。
Master, Master, wake up.
少爷，少爷，醒醒吧。
Master.
少爷。
Master, you seem to be having a nightmare.
少爷，您好像 做噩梦了。
I am fine.
我很好。
I suddenly remembered a lot of things I had always remembered
我突然想起了很多 我一直记得的事情
But I hope I can forget it.
但希望能够忘记。
Is uncle in the villa?
叔叔在别墅里吗？
he is.
他是。
OK
好的。
Go pick him up
去接他吧
and He Jiuling.
and He Jiuling.
I decided to tell her
我决定告诉她
I have recovered.
我已经康复了。
At.
于。
are you sure?
你确定吗？
Have you really recovered?
你真的康复了吗？
Three thousand volumes of poetry collection
诗集三千册
and countless numerology,
以及无数的数字命理，
I remember them all.
我都记得他们。
God really bless our Rong family.
真是上天保佑我们荣家。
God bless Xingxiang Pavilion.
上天保佑星象阁。
I'm going
我要去
tell the world,
告诉世界，
All guests are invited,
邀请所有嘉宾，
Let everyone know you are okay.
让每个人都知道你一切都好。
Uncle, the birthday party is coming soon
叔叔，生日宴会即将来临
It should be the biggest event in Beijing.
应该是京城最大的盛事。
I can't steal the spotlight.
我不能抢风头。
We won’t talk about that for now.
我们暂时不谈这个。
What's more, in these years, I have also seen the warmth and warmth of people's hearts.
更何况，这些年，也见识了 人心的冷暖。
After this experience, I saw it through.
经过这次经历，我看透了。
Whether outsiders know it or not
不管外人知道与否
it is not important.
并不重要。
Well, whatever you say.
好吧，随你怎么说。
We'll wait until the birthday party is over,
我们就等生日宴会结束后，
And held a small banquet for the people of Xingxiang Pavilion
并为星象阁的人举办小型宴会
let them know
让他们知道
Their star picker is back.
他们的摘星师回来了。
Then I'll make arrangements now.
那我现在就去安排。
Thanks.
谢谢。
Don't say that.
别这么说。
I'm glad you're okay.
我很高兴你没事。
I'll go tell Cheng Bi and Tan.
我去告诉城碧和谭。
They were also very helpful.
他们也提供了很多帮助。
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
If you have something to say, please say it later. I'll leave now.
如果你有什么话要说， 请稍后再说。我现在就离开。
when we get married,
当我们结婚时，
No formal proposals or gifts,
没有正式的求婚或礼物，
I didn’t meet my parents,
没有和父母见面，
No friends or relatives were present,
没有朋友和亲戚在场，
And there is no wedding dress.
而且没有婚纱。
What's worse is that that day,
更糟糕的是，那天，
You have lost your closest family member.
你失去了最亲密的家人。
This is the beginning of your nightmare.
这是你噩梦的开始。
Where in the world can there be such a bad wedding?
世界上哪里有 这么糟糕的婚礼
And such an unfortunate bride?
还有这么不幸的新娘？
From what I've seen,
从我所看到的地方来看，
this is not right.
这是不对的。
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
??? 我写下的对你的渴望？？？
You deserve a great wedding.
你值得拥有一场盛大的婚礼。
He Jiuling.
He Jiuling.
After the Queen Mother’s birthday banquet,
太后寿宴结束后，
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 命运无路可逃？？？
Let's get a divorce.
我们离婚吧。
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
??? 我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤？？？
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河???
???You quietly turned around and closed the marriage certificate? ? ?
??? 你悄悄转身 合上了婚书？？？
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
??? 原来你就是我的不解之缘？？？
OK
好的。
How could you say such a thing to Madam?
你怎么能对夫人说这种话？
Is it because of last night?
是因为昨晚的原因吗？
Should I...
我是不是该...
There is really no need to do this.
实在没有必要这么做。
Let's hear what the lady has to say
我们来听听夫人怎么说吧
And then make a decision?
然后做出决定？
Why are you in such a hurry to go to Xingxiang Pavilion now?
现在急着去星象阁干什么？
【Rongfu】 The wife is the most important.
【容府】 夫人最重要。
Master.
少爷。
Master, are you willing to listen to me?
少爷，你愿意听我说吗？
miss.
错过。
Have something to eat.
吃点东西吧。
Let's go find our senior brother.
我们去找师兄吧。
Has he really decided to break up with He Jiuling?
他真的决定 要和贺九菱分手了吗？
I understand what's going on.
我明白是怎么回事了。
Now that Yu has made up his mind,
既然宇已经下定决心了，
Then,
然后，
The astrology center will be closer to the Princess Mansion.
占星馆会更 靠近公主府。
Let those who are bald enough
让那些够秃头的人
Holding out hope for marrying the princess.
为迎娶公主抱有希望。
go.
去。
Send some supplements to the princess mansion.
给公主府送一些补品。
Make sure to attract more attention.
确保吸引更多关注。
Yes.
是的。
I now have a general understanding.
我现在有了一个大概的了解。
The star map is the luck obtained by the ancestors of the Rong family
星图是荣家先祖得来的幸运
When the Astrology Institute was established.
占星馆成立时。
There is a hidden room in the pavilion
亭子里有一个隐藏的房间
It was strictly guarded.
那是被严格看守的。
No one else is allowed to come near
其他人不得靠近
Or see it with your own eyes.
或亲眼所见。
People who have seen star maps
看过星图的人
No questions will be answered.
不会回答任何问题。
Everyone is very alert.
所有人都非常警惕。
I have sent people to investigate many times
我多次派人去调查
But nothing came of it.
但没有任何结果。
Never seen before, not allowed to come near.
从未见过，不准靠近。
How do I know what I need to destroy?
我怎么知道 我需要销毁什么
When the goal is unclear?
当目标还不清楚的时候？
A painting? a book?
一幅画？一本书？
Just destroy them all.
只要将其全部摧毁即可。
Because we have no idea what it is,
因为我们根本不知道它是什么，
Let's burn it all with fire.
让我们用火把它全部烧掉吧。
I'll think about it again.
我会再考虑一下。
Do you want me to think of another way?
你要我想别的办法吗？
You've done enough for me.
你为我做的已经够多了。
from now on,
今后，
I'll handle it myself.
我自己来处理。
You are afraid that I will be exposed
你怕我暴露
I don't want to get you involved either.
我也不想把你也卷入其中。
Apart from,
除了，
The days when I was the lady of the Astrology Pavilion
我当占星阁夫人的日子
It won't be long.
不会太久。
I need to take advantage of it.
我需要好好利用它。
Rong Yu said
Rong Yu said
He wants a divorce.
他想离婚。
Wouldn't that be perfect?
那不是很完美吗？
You two shouldn't
你们两个不应该
Tie together in this identity.
在这个身份中联系在一起。
It was wrong for you two to get married from the start.
你们两个结婚从一开始就是错误的。
that's right.
这是正确的。
You don't look happy.
你看起来不太高兴。
Ling, I'm just worried about you.
玲，我只是担心你。
What you gave to Rong Yu already
你给容羽的已经
More than you should give.
超出了你应该给予的。
guilt or debt
内疚或负债
It shouldn't be presented like this.
不应该这样呈现。
Could it be...
难道是……
forget it. It doesn't matter.
忘了它。没关系。
Yes.
是的。
Yes. Yes.
是的。是的。
I like him.
我喜欢他。
Do you hear your own voice?
你听到自己的声音了吗？
I know exactly what I'm talking about.
我很清楚我在说什么。
I try to deceive myself not to think so
我试图欺骗自己 不这么想
but I can not.
但我不能。
indeed.
的确。
He doesn't have any characteristics
他没有任何一个特质
This fits with what I generally consider a person attractive.
这符合我通常 认为的一个人的吸引力。
He is weak and fragile,
他是软弱且脆弱的，
Expensive and troublesome.
又贵又麻烦。
However, I just like him.
然而，我就是喜欢他。
I don't know when I started feeling like this
我不知道什么时候开始有这样的感觉
But now I can't help myself.
但现在我无法自拔。
How could you like...
你怎么会喜欢...
Someone like him?
像他这样的人？
He was still poisoned.
他还是中毒了。
Are you talking about amnesia fans?
你说的是失忆粉吗？
But no one will forget this feeling, right?
但没有人会忘记 这份感情，对吗？
This amnesia fan
这个失忆粉
It should be called lovesickness.
应该叫相思病。
It turns out that this is a yearning heart
原来这就是一颗相思之心
feel like.
感觉像。
In your eyes,
在你眼里，
He is a fool.
他是个傻瓜。
but what i saw
但我所看到的
He is a simple Rong Yu.
是一个单纯的容宇。
I've thought about it.
我已经考虑过了。
if he can't protect me
如果他不能保护我
I can protect him.
我可以保护他。
if he can't do anything
如果他什么也做不了的话
I just hope
我只是希望
he can stay
他可以留下来
Happy and cheerful.
快乐开朗。
Now, he has given up drugs.
现在，他已经戒毒了。
Senior brother, everything is fine now.
师兄，现在一切都好了。
He became a member of the Astrology Pavilion again
他再次成为占星阁的人
The young master is loved and respected by everyone.
少爷，受到所有人的爱戴和尊敬。
Ling.
凌.
I can rest assured now.
我现在可以放心了。
The condition of your hands.
你的手部状况。
I'm afraid it'll never get better
恐怕永远不会好起来
But that's fine.
但这很好。
It reminds me all the time
它可以时时提醒我
It's not because of guilt
这不是因为内疚
or liabilities,
或负债，
But sixteen-year-old He Jiuling
但十六岁的何九龄
Stand before him with pure sincerity.
以纯粹的真诚站在他的面前。
Do you like him that much?
你就那么喜欢他吗？
so many?
那么多？
what does that mean?
这意味着什么？
All I know is that I was desperate
我只知道我当时很绝望
especially when i know
尤其是当我知道
I must destroy the astrology center
我必须摧毁占星馆
And killed Jiang Rong.
并杀了姜蓉。
???Under the sunset at dusk? ? ?
??? 黄昏夕阳下？？？
???I traveled thousands of miles to a distant place? ? ?
??? 我千里迢迢去远方？？？
???Playing the piano under the moonlight? ? ?
??? 月下弹琴？？？
???These drinks won’t make me forget? ? ?
??? 这些饮料不会让我忘记？？？
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
??? 我写下的对你的渴望？？？
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 我们的命运是写在纸上的？？？
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 就像最烈的酒一样？？？
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 命运无路可逃？？？
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
??? 回头一看，我看到你在等待？？？
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
??? 我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤？？？
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河???
???You quietly turned around and closed the marriage certificate? ? ?
??? 你悄悄转身 合上了婚书？？？
???Ask how many stars are there in the sky? ? ?
??? 问天上有多少颗星星？？？
???The desire I wrote for you? ? ?
??? 我写下的对你的渴望？？？
??? Our destiny is written on paper? ? ?
??? 我们的命运是写在纸上的？？？
??? Like the strongest wine? ? ?
??? 就像最烈的酒一样？？？
??? There is no way to escape fate? ? ?
??? 命运无路可逃？？？
???Looking back, I saw you waiting? ? ?
??? 回头一看，我看到你在等待？？？
???Our life is full of joy and sorrow? ? ?
??? 我们的生活充满欢乐和悲伤？？？
??? Desire to crystallize into a bright galaxy???
??? 渴望结晶 成明亮的银河???
???I gently caress the guzheng, waiting for passers-by like you???
??? 我轻轻抚着古筝， 等待着你这样的路人???
???So you are my indissoluble bond? ? ?
??? 原来你就是我的不解之缘？？？